<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fpdoc-descriptions>
  <package name="mqttcomponents">
    <module name="mqttserver">
      <element name="TMQTTServer.OnAccepted">
        <short>Event occurs when a connection is accepted by the server</short>
      </element>
      <element name="TMQTTServer.OnDisconnected">
        <short>Event fires when a connection is disconnected by the client</short>
      </element>
      <element name="TMQTTServerSession.Disconnect">
        <short>Call to disconnect the session</short>
        <descr>This method sets Connected to False and then fires the OnDisconnect event handler.  It is intended to be used to provide integration with a networking stack.</descr>
      </element>
      <element name="TMQTTServerSession.Disconnected">
        <short>This method is called when the client disconnects from the server</short>
      </element>
      <element name="TMQTTServerSession.Bail">
        <short>This method disconnects the connection with an error message</short>
        <descr>This method is used to abort connections due to various protocol violations.  It throws an exception.</descr>
      </element>
      <element name="TMQTTServer.AllowNullClientIDs">
        <short>Allow clients who connect with null ClientIDs to be assigned random ClientIDs</short>
        <descr>Default is True.  When set to false, clients connecting with NULL ClientIDs will recieve MQTT_CONNACK_CLIENTID_REJECTED</descr>
      </element>
      <element name="TMQTTServer.RequireAuthentication">
        <short>Require clients to provide a valid username and password to connect</short>
        <descr>If false, a username and password will be validated if it is provided but connections where no username and password are provided will also be allowed.  If a username and password are provided, the session will be associated with a user object.  The default is false.</descr>
      </element>
      <element name="TMQTTServerSession.InitializeNetworkConnection">
        <short>Initializes a server network connection from a CONNECT packet and returns a CONNACK response code.</short>
      </element>
      <element name="TMQTTServerSession.InitSessionState">
        <short>Initializes a session state from a CONNECT packet at returns true if this is a resumed session</short>
      </element>
      <element name="TMQTTServer.Enabled">
        <short>Setting Enabled to false will prevent the server from accepting new connections</short>
      </element>
      <element name="TMQTTServer.KeepAlive">
        <short>The number of seconds of inactivity before a client connection times out</short>
      </element>
      <element name="TMQTTServer.StrictClientIDValidation">
        <short>If True, ClientIDs may only contain letters and numbers</short>
      </element>
      <short>The MQTT Server component</short>
    <element name="TMQTTServerConnection.CheckTerminateSession"><short>Terminates the session if it was automatically generated as a result of a client passing a blank clientID</short><descr>Sessions where the clientid is automatically generated by the server are cannot be saved for later retrieval because the clientid does not know what clientid was assigned.</descr>
      </element><element name="TMQTTServerConnection.Disconnect"><short>Initiates the disconnect process</short>
      </element><element name="TMQTTServerConnection.Disconnected"><short>Responds to a client disconnecting the network connection.</short><descr>If a client connection terminates unexpectedly the server sends the will message associated with that connection if one was provided.</descr>
      </element><element name="TMQTTServerConnection.Bail"><descr>When the server detects a protocol error it should drop the network connection.</descr>
      </element><element name="TMQTTServerConnection.Publish"><short>Sends an MQTT PUBLISH message to the client</short><descr>Topic: The topic string
Data: The message payload
QoS: The QoS to use while sending the message
Retain: The status of the retain flag in the message
Duplicate: The status of the duplicate flag in the message

When sending a PUBLISH Packet to a Client the Server MUST set the RETAIN flag to 1 if a message is sent as a result of a new subscription being made by a Client [MQTT-3.3.1-8]. 

It MUST set the RETAIN flag to 0 when a PUBLISH Packet is sent to a Client because it matches an established subscription regardless of how the flag was set in the message it received [MQTT-3.3.1-9].</descr>
      </element><element name="TMQTTSession.SendRetainedMessages"><short>For each subscription in the list, send any retained messages</short><descr>When a client subscribes to a topic, any retained messages stored on the server should be sent to the client with the retain flag set to true.</descr>
      </element><element name="TMQTTSession.MaximumQOS"><short>The maximum QOS at which the session can publish messages</short><descr>This property forces a QoS downgrade for particular clients that can't handle all QoS levels</descr>
      </element><element name="TMQTTServer.MaximumQOS"><short>Force the server to downgrade the QoS of all messages published</short><descr>The server can still recieve messages at any QoS level but will limit the QoS of any messages it sends.</descr>
      </element>
    <element name="TMQTTServerThread"><short>TMQTTServerThread calls TMQTTServer.HandleTimer every second</short>
      </element><element name="TMQTTServerConnectionList"><short>Maintains a list of TMQTTServerConnection objects</short>
      </element><element name="TMQTTServerConnectionList.Clear"><short>Frees all the connections in the list and clears the list</short>
      </element><element name="TMQTTServerConnectionList.Destroy"/><element name="TMQTTServerConnectionList.Create"><short>Creates a server connection list</short>
      </element><element name="TMQTTServerConnectionList.Add"><short>Adds a connection to  the list</short>
      </element><element name="TMQTTServerConnectionList.Remove"><short>Removes a connection from the list.  Does not close or free the connection</short>
      </element><element name="TMQTTServerConnectionList.Delete"><short>Deletes the connection at index'th position in the Items array.  Does not close or free the connection.</short>
      </element><element name="TMQTTSession"><short>Represents an MQTT Session.  </short><descr>A session may persist between different connections, i.e. a client may reconnect to an existing session.</descr>
      </element>
    </module>
    <short>MQTT client and server components</short>
  </package>
</fpdoc-descriptions>
